parachat.com 2004-06-03

# ParaChat FAQ

### **ParaChat Privacy Policy**

ParaChat Group takes your privacy seriously. To learn more about ParaChat Group's privacy policy, please read our policy below.

The Federal Trade Commission offers information about [ surfing the Internet safely](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.html).

**Privacy Policy Coverage**

This Privacy Policy covers ParaChat Group's treatment of personally identifiable information that ParaChat Group collects when you are on the ParaChat.com Web site, and when you use ParaChat Group's products and/or services. This policy also covers ParaChat Group's treatment of any personally identifiable information that ParaChat Group's business partners share with ParaChat Group or that ParaChat Group may collect on a partner or third-party site.

This policy does not apply to the content or practices of companies or Web sites that ParaChat Group does not own or control, or to people that ParaChat Group does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

ParaChat Group collects personally identifiable information when you use certain ParaChat Group products and/or services, when you visit ParaChat Group web pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. ParaChat Group may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 

When you license free ParaChat Group products, we ask for your email address, and for permission to fulfill your requests via email for certain products and services, to contact you about specials and new products, and/or to fulfill your requests for third-party promotions. By providing this information to ParaChat Group, you may be limiting your anonymity to us.

When you license paid ParaChat Group products, we ask for your name, address, zip code, email address, and credit card information. Once you provide this information to ParaChat Group, you are not anonymous to us. Information provided with regard to paid ParaChat Group products is retained for internal use only, and is not shared with any third party. As a customer, you may receive product and service updates directly from ParaChat Group, or from third parties if you have provided consent to do so.

ParaChat Group also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, when you visit our Web site, or utilize our hosted products.

ParaChat Group uses information for three general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to contact you about specials and new products, and to fulfill third-party promotional material that you may have requested.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

ParaChat Group will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. ParaChat Group may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;  

  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;  

  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of ParaChat Group to provide a product or service to you.  

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or  

  * We find that your actions on our web site, or by using a hosted product, violate the License Agreement or Guidelines to which you have agreed, or to which you were requested to adhere, for specific products or services.  

**Third Party Advertising**

We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [please click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php).

**Cookies**

ParaChat Group may set and access ParaChat Group cookies on your computer. ParaChat Group allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, and not ParaChat Group's Privacy Policy. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to ParaChat Group's cookies.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Editing and Deleting Your Product and/or Account Information**

To edit and/or delete your product and/or account information that has already been provided by you to ParaChat Group, including whether you want ParaChat Group to contact you about specials and new products, please contact our [support team](mailto:support@parachat.com?subject=) for instructions. You may also follow the instructions for editing and/or deleting product and/or account information that were provided to you when your service was initiated, or for mailing list addition or deletion using the instructions that are included in a mailing list email that you may have received.

**Security**

Your security when ordering ParaChat Group products is primary concern. In certain areas, ParaChat Group uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. Our secure server is called "pro.parachatgroup.com", Organization = M Square, Inc., Organizational Unit = ParaChat. You may verify that the form you are using is a secure form, and is consistent with the site that you are visiting, by clicking on the Secure Site icon on each of ParaChat Group's secure order forms and Web pages.

Information pertaining to certain ParaChat hosted products is password-protected for your privacy and security.

**Policy for Individuals Under the Age of 13**

ParaChat is intended for individuals age 13 and over only. We do not provide content for children. Parents should closely monitor content visited by children, and review privacy policies on all Web sites to determine whether content is acceptable for children.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

ParaChat Group may amend this policy from time to time without notice. Please review our Privacy Policy regularly. If substantial changes are made that effect the way in which ParaChat Group handles your personally identifiable information, a reasonable effort will be utilized to contact you, and/or ParaChat Group will post a notice on our site.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have any questions or suggestions, please contact our [support team](mailto:support@parachat.com?subject=).
